import 'model/class.dart';
List<Quiz>questions = [
   Quiz(question:'1.What is the chemical symbol for water?', options:['H2O','CO2','Mg','si'],
    indexOfAnswer:0),
    Quiz(question:'2.Who is First Prime Minister of india?', options:['Rahul Gandhi','Javaharlal Nehuru','Mahadma Gandhi','Barak obama'],
     indexOfAnswer:1),
     Quiz(question:'3.Flutter provided by...', options:['Amazone','Meta','Google','x'],
      indexOfAnswer:2),
      Quiz(question:'4.What is the correct plural form of "mouse"?', options:[ 'Mouses','Mices','Mouse', 'Mice' ],
      indexOfAnswer:3),
     Quiz(question:'5.Which of the following is an example of a compound word?', options:['Boy','Running','Sunflower','quickly'],
      indexOfAnswer:2),
];
List<Quiz>sportsquestions  = [
   Quiz(question:'1.What is the national sport of India?',
    options:['Hockey','football','Kabaddi','Cricket'],
    indexOfAnswer:0),
    Quiz(question:'2.The Olympics are held every how many years?', 
    options:['3','2 ','4','8'],
     indexOfAnswer:2),
     Quiz(question:'3.Which country is football from?',
      options:['Britain','China','India','Iran'],
      indexOfAnswer:0),
      Quiz(question:'4.How many players are on a basketball team.?', 
      options:[ '2','3','5','1' ],
      indexOfAnswer:2),
     Quiz(question:'5.What is the name of the sport where players compete to swim, bike, and run the fastest?', 
     options:['Rugby','Triathlon','tennis','Boxing'],
      indexOfAnswer:1),
];
List<Quiz>historyquestions  = [
   Quiz(question:'1.Which country were the targets of atomic bombs dropped by the United States in 1945?',
    options:['Japan','India','london','toronto'],
    indexOfAnswer:0),
    Quiz(question:'2.Which ancient civilization is credited with building the pyramids in Giza, Egypt?', 
    options:['Mesopotamia','Ancient Egypt','indus valley','Ancient China'],
     indexOfAnswer:2),
     Quiz(question:'3.The Cold War was a geopolitical tension primarily between which two superpowers?',
      options:['US and USSR','china and Us','Uk and Ussr','Us and Uk'],
      indexOfAnswer:0),
      Quiz(question:'4.In 1917, which event led to the overthrow of the Russian Provisional Government and the ?', 
      options:['October Revolution','Russian civilWAr','Red october','June Revolution'],
      indexOfAnswer:1),
     Quiz(question:'5.Which city served as the capital of the Ottoman Empire for over 400 years?', 
     options:['Cairo','Istanbul','Tehran','Kabul'],
      indexOfAnswer:1),
];
List<Quiz>techquestions  = [
   Quiz(question:'1.Which search engine is known for its "Im Feeling Lucky" button?',
    options:['Google','Bing','Yahoo','DuckDuckGo'],
    indexOfAnswer:0),
    Quiz(question:'2.Which operating system is developed by Apple Inc?', 
    options:['Windows','MacOS','Linux','Android'],
     indexOfAnswer:2),
     Quiz(question:'3.What is the term for a small software program that adds functionality to a web browser?',
      options:['Plugins','widget','app','Extention'],
      indexOfAnswer:0),
      Quiz(question:'4.What is the name of the device used to input data by pressing keys ?', 
      options:['Moniter','Keyboard','Mouse','CPU'],
      indexOfAnswer:1),
     Quiz(question:'5.What type of software helps protect your computer from malicious programs and viruses?', 
     options:['Firewell','Antivirus','spredsheet','Browser'],
      indexOfAnswer:1),
];